University of Connecticut 1998.0185
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1935-1962
  - 1957-1958
    - J (Box 16:, Folder 71)
    - Kellogg, W. K. Foundation (Box 16:, Folder 72)
    - Ki (Box 16:, Folder 73)
    - L (Box 16:, Folder 74)
    - Labor Management Institute (Box 16:, Folder 75)
    - Land Grant College Association - Executive Committee (Box 16:, Folder 76)
    - Legislation, State (Box 16:, Folder 77)
    - Life Science Building (Box 16:, Folder 78)
    - Mackie, Helen (Trustee) (Box 16:, Folder 79)
    - Mahoney, Mary (Trustee) (Box 16:, Folder 80)
    - Manning, Stuart - Acting co - director, Univ. Extension (Box 16:, Folder 81)
    - Marsh, E. Lear, Jr. (Box 16:, Folder 82)
    - May, Elizabeth E. - Dean, School of Economics (Box 16:, Folder 83)
    - Medical - Dental school (Box 16:, Folder 84)
    - Military Day (Box 16:, Folder 85)
    - Military Department (Box 16:, Folder 86)
    - Mo (Box 17:, Folder 1)
    - National Advisory Council on Rural Civil Defense (Box 17:, Folder 2)
    - National Association of State Universities (Box 17:, Folder 3)
    - National Education Association (Box 17:, Folder 4)
    - National Research Council, 1957-1958 (Box 17:, Folder 5)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 17:, Folder 6)
    - Nelson, Don (Box 17:, Folder 7)
    - New buildings (Box 17:, Folder 8)
    - New England Board of Higher Education (Box 17:, Folder 9)
    - New England Land Grant State Universities (Box 17:, Folder 10)
    - Northby, Arwood S. - Director of Student Personnel (Box 17:, Folder 11)
    - Nuclear reactor (Box 17:, Folder 12)
    - P (Box 17:, Folder 13)
    - Parking (Box 17:, Folder 14)
    - Pharmacy research addition (Box 17:, Folder 15)
    - Powers, John E. - Placement (Box 17:, Folder 16)
    - President's Committee on Education Beyond the High School (Box 17:, Folder 17)
    - President's Committee on Scientists and Engineers (Box 17:, Folder 18)
    - Public Works Department - Timothy J. Murphy, Jr., Comm. (Box 17:, Folder 19)
    - R (Box 17:, Folder 20)
    - Research foundation (Box 17:, Folder 21)
    - Research grants (Box 17:, Folder 22)
    - Research grants summary for mimeo list, 1957-1958 (Box 17:, Folder 23)
    - Real estate (Box 17:, Folder 24)
    - Riccio, L. C. - Comptroller of University (Box 17:, Folder 25)
    - Sanders, William J. (Trustee) (Box 17:, Folder 26)
    - Schneller, Richard F. (Trustee) (Box 17:, Folder 27)
    - Science talent awards (Box 17:, Folder 28)
    - Shippee, Lester E. (trustee, chairman) (Box 17:, Folder 29)
    - Sistare, Willard M. - Manger of Auditorium (Box 17:, Folder 30)
    - Speeches (Box 17:, Folder 31)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 17:, Folder 32)
    - State Building Commission (Box 17:, Folder 33)
    - State Personnel Division - Glendon A. Scoboria, Dir. (Box 17:, Folder 34)
    - Student Senate - Al Hajjar, President (Box 17:, Folder 35)
    - Student Union board and building - Thomas E. Ahearn, manager, 1957 September 10 (Box 17:, Folder 36)
    - T.V. (Box 17:, Folder 37)
    - Television and Museum (Box 17:, Folder 38)
    - To (Box 17:, Folder 39)
    - Torgerson, Harold - Dean, School of Engineering (Box 17:, Folder 40)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. - Dean, School of Social Work (Box 17:, Folder 41)
    - U (Box 17:, Folder 42)
    - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Box 17:, Folder 43)
    - University Scholars (Box 17:, Folder 44)
    - University secondary schools (Box 17:, Folder 45)
    - University Security Police - Larry Goodale (Box 17:, Folder 46)
    - University Senate, 1957-1958 (Box 17:, Folder 47)
    - Van Bibber, E. G. - Director, School of Phys. Education (Box 17:, Folder 48)
    - Veterinary Science Building (Box 17:, Folder 49)
    - Von der Mehden, J. Louis - Memorial Rehearsal and Recital Hall (Box 17:, Folder 50)
    - Waterbury Branch - Patrick E. Fontane, Jr., Supervisor (Box 17:, Folder 51)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Trustee) (Box 17:, Folder 52)
    - Waugh, Albert E. - Provost (Box 17:, Folder 53)
    - We (Box 17:, Folder 54)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. - Dean of the Graduate School (Box 17:, Folder 55)
    - Wide, Wide World (Box 17:, Folder 56)
    - Widmer, Carolyn L. - Dean, School of Nursing (Box 17:, Folder 57)
    - Young, Wilfred B. - Dean, College of Agriculture (Box 17:, Folder 58)
  - 1958-1959
    - A (Box 17:, Folder 59)
    - Ackerman, Laurence J. - Dean, School of Bus. Admin. (Box 17:, Folder 60)
    - Administrative Reports (Box 17:, Folder 61)
    - Advisers (Box 17:, Folder 62)
    - Air Force (Box 17:, Folder 63)
    - Alcorn, Paul - Director, Library (Box 17:, Folder 64)
    - Alumni (Box 17:, Folder 65)
    - American Council on Education (Box 17:, Folder 66)
    - American Council - Higher Education and Nat'l Affairs (Box 17:, Folder 67)
    - American Council - report on questionnaires (Box 17:, Folder 68)
    - American Council - Special Committee on Sponsored Research (Box 17:, Folder 69)
    - An (Box 17:, Folder 70)
    - Architects (Box 17:, Folder 71)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 17:, Folder 72)
    - B (Box 18:, Folder 1)
    - Bailey, Clark (Box 18:, Folder 2)
    - Be (Box 18:, Folder 3)
    - Benton, William (Trustee) (Box 18:, Folder 4)
    - Bequests (Box 18:, Folder 5)
    - Bi (Box 18:, Folder 6)
    - Biographical data (Box 18:, Folder 7)
    - Bishop, Merlin D. (Trustee) (Box 18:, Folder 8)
    - Bo (Box 18:, Folder 9)
    - Board material (Box 18:, Folder 10)
    - Borge, Victor (Box 18:, Folder 11)
    - Brock, C. Raymond (Trustee) (Box 18:, Folder 12)
    - Brammell, P. Roy - Dean, School of Education (Box 18:, Folder 13)
    - Budds, John J. (Trustee) (Box 18:, Folder 14)
    - Budget (Box 18:, Folder 15)
    - Budget Division, State (Box 18:, Folder 16)
    - Campus (Box 18:, Folder 17)
    - Capital projects (Box 18:, Folder 18)
    - Carter, W. Harrison, - Dean, College of Arts and Sciences (Box 18:, Folder 19)
    - Christian, J.O. - Director Div. Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 18:, Folder 20)
    - Civil Defense (Box 18:, Folder 21)
    - Co (Box 18:, Folder 22)
    - Cohen, Sumner - Men's Housing (Box 18:, Folder 23)
    - Commencement (Box 18:, Folder 24)
    - Commencement at Iowa City - A. N. Jorgensen (Box 18:, Folder 25)
    - Committee Letters (Box 18:, Folder 26)
    - Committee reports (Box 18:, Folder 27)
    - Compulsory attendance (Box 18:, Folder 28)
    - Connecticut Association of Real Estate Boards (Box 18:, Folder 29)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 18:, Folder 30)
    - Connecticut Council for Pre-college Science Education, Inc. (Box 18:, Folder 31)
    - Contracts (Box 18:, Folder 32)
    - Coo (Box 18:, Folder 33)
    - Crane, Carl - University Extension (Box 18:, Folder 34)
    - D (Box 18:, Folder 35)
    - Deans and directors (Box 18:, Folder 36)
    - Do (Box 18:, Folder 37)
    - Donahue, A. J. (Trustee) (Box 18:, Folder 38)
    - E (Box 18:, Folder 39)
    - Education, State Department of (Box 18:, Folder 40)
    - F (Box 18:, Folder 41)
    - Fees (Box 18:, Folder 42)
    - Finance and Control, Dept. of - G. J. Conkling, Commissioner (Box 18:, Folder 43)
    - Financial Aid (Box 18:, Folder 44)
    - Fine Arts Building (Box 18:, Folder 45)
    - Fingles, Franklin O. (Box 18:, Folder 46)
    - Fo (Box 18:, Folder 47)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 18:, Folder 48)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 18:, Folder 49)
    - Fuller, Alfred C. (Trustee) (Box 18:, Folder 50)
    - Ge (Box 18:, Folder 51)
    - Gill, Joseph H. - Commissioner of Agriculture (Trustee) (Box 18:, Folder 52)
    - Gleason, John H. - Director, Div. Of Communications (Box 18:, Folder 53)
    - Goodchild, F.M. - Director Div. Health Service (Box 18:, Folder 54)
    - Governor of Connecticut - A.A. Ribicoff (Box 18:, Folder 55)
    - Gr (Box 18:, Folder 56)
    - H (Box 18:, Folder 57)
    - Har, 1958-1959 (Box 18:, Folder 58)
    - Hartford Branch - Wilbur R. Griswold, Supervisor (Box 18:, Folder 59)
    - Hewitt, Harold G. - Dean, School of Pharmacy (Box 18:, Folder 60)
    - Hi (Box 18:, Folder 61)
    - Honors Day (Box 18:, Folder 62)
    - Hopkins, Bert E. - Dean, School of Law (Box 18:, Folder 63)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency (Box 18:, Folder 64)
    - I (Box 18:, Folder 65)
    - Institute of Cellular Biology (Box 18:, Folder 66)
    - Institute, Counseling and Guidance Training - E.A. Wicas, Director (Box 18:, Folder 67)
    - Institute of Gerontology - Don P. Kent, director (Box 18:, Folder 68)
    - Institute of Marine Research - John S. Rankin, director (Box 18:, Folder 69)
    - Institute for Secondary School Teachers of Physics (Box 18:, Folder 70)
    - Institute for Teacher of Science (Box 18:, Folder 71)
    - Joint Council on Educational TV (est.), 1951 April 1 (Box 18:, Folder 72)
    - K (Box 18:, Folder 73)
    - Legislation, Federal (Box 18:, Folder 74)
    - Legislation, State (Box 18:, Folder 75)
    - Liaison Committee (Box 18:, Folder 76)
    - Life Science Building (Box 18:, Folder 77)
    - Lo (Box 18:, Folder 78)
    - Mackie, Helen (Trustee) (Box 18:, Folder 79)
    - Mahoney, Mary (Trustee) (Box 18:, Folder 80)
    - Manning, Stuart - University Extension (Box 18:, Folder 81)
    - Mansfield, J. Kenneth (Trustee) (Box 18:, Folder 82)
    - Medical - Dental School (Box 18:, Folder 83)
    - Military Day (Box 18:, Folder 84)
    - Military Department (Box 18:, Folder 85)
    - National Advisory Council on Rural Civil Defense (Box 18:, Folder 86)
    - National Association of State Universities (Box 18:, Folder 87)
    - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 18:, Folder 88)
    - National Planning Association (Box 18:, Folder 89)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 18:, Folder 90)
    - Nelson, Don (Box 18:, Folder 91)
    - New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 18:, Folder 92)
    - New England Board of Higher Education (Box 18:, Folder 93)
    - New England Land Grant State Universities (Box 18:, Folder 94)
    - Northby, Arwood S. - Director, Student Personnel (Box 19:, Folder 1)
    - Nuclear reactor (Box 19:, Folder 2)
    - P (Box 19:, Folder 3)
    - Peterson, Mary Elizabeth (Trustee) (Box 19:, Folder 4)
    - Pharmacy Research addition (Box 19:, Folder 5)
    - Pictures, 1958-1959 (Box 19:, Folder 6)
    - Powers, John E. - Placement (Box 19:, Folder 7)
    - Public Works Department (Box 19:, Folder 8)
    - Re (Box 19:, Folder 9)
    - Real estate (Box 19:, Folder 10)
    - Regional Vocational Agricultural Center (Box 19:, Folder 11)
    - Religious Education (Box 19:, Folder 12)
    - Research foundation (Box 19:, Folder 13)
    - Research grants (Box 19:, Folder 14)
    - Research grants for publication (Box 19:, Folder 15)
    - Retirement certificates (Box 19:, Folder 16)
    - Reccio, Leonard C. - University comptroller (Box 19:, Folder 17)
    - Ro (Box 19:, Folder 18)
    - Rock, Robert W. - Coordinator, Student Activities (Box 19:, Folder 19)
    - Ryan, J. Ray (Trustee) (Box 19:, Folder 20)
    - Sanders, William J. (Trustee) (Box 19:, Folder 21)
    - Schneller, Richard F. (Trustee) (Box 19:, Folder 22)
    - Science talent awards (Box 19:, Folder 23)
    - Shippee, Lester E. (Trustee) (Box 19:, Folder 24)
    - Sistare, Willard M. - Manager Auditorium (Box 19:, Folder 25)
    - Sm (Box 19:, Folder 26)
    - South dormitories (for girls) (Box 19:, Folder 27)
    - Speeches (Box 19:, Folder 28)
    - Spielman, Arless A. (Box 19:, Folder 29)
    - St (Box 19:, Folder 30)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 19:, Folder 31)
    - State Building Commission (Box 19:, Folder 32)
    - State Highway Department (Box 19:, Folder 33)
    - State Personnel Division (Box 19:, Folder 34)
    - State Public Utilities (Box 19:, Folder 35)
    - State Universities Assn. (Box 19:, Folder 36)
    - Student Senate (Box 19:, Folder 37)
    - Student Senate coffee (Box 19:, Folder 38)
    - Student Union board and building (Box 19:, Folder 39)
    - Summer theater (Box 19:, Folder 40)
    - TV (Box 19:, Folder 41)
    - Torgerson, Harold - Dean, School of Engineering (Box 19:, Folder 42)
    - Trail, J. M. (Box 19:, Folder 43)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. - Dean, School of Social Work (Box 19:, Folder 44)
    - U (Box 19:, Folder 45)
    - U.S.D.A. (Box 19:, Folder 46)
    - U.S. Dept. Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 19:, Folder 47)
    - University scholars (Box 19:, Folder 48)
    - University secondary school, 1958-1959 (Box 19:, Folder 49)
    - University Senate (Box 19:, Folder 50)
    - V (Box 19:, Folder 51)
    - Van Bibber, E. George - Dir., School of Physical Educ. (Box 19:, Folder 52)
    - Veterinary Science Building (Box 19:, Folder 53)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 19:, Folder 54)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Trustee) (Box 19:, Folder 55)
    - Waugh, Albert E. - Provost (Box 19:, Folder 56)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. - Dean, Graduate School (Box 20:, Folder 1)
    - W.H.U.S. (Box 20:, Folder 2)
    - Wi (Box 20:, Folder 3)
    - Widmer, Carolyn L. - Dean, School of Nursing (Box 20:, Folder 4)
    - Wo (Box 20:, Folder 5)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 20:, Folder 6)
    - Young, Wilfred B. - Dean, College of Agriculture (Box 20:, Folder 7)
    - Hold File (Box 20:, Folder 8)
  - 1959-1960
    - A (Box 20:, Folder 9)
    - Ackerman, Laurence J. - Dean, School of Business Adm. (Box 20:, Folder 10)
    - Administrative reports (Box 20:, Folder 11)
    - Advisers (Box 20:, Folder 12)
    - Air Force (Box 20:, Folder 13)
    - Alumni (Box 20:, Folder 14)
    - American Council on Education (Box 20:, Folder 15)
    - American Council - Higher Education and National Affairs (Box 20:, Folder 16)
    - American Council - report on questionnaires (Box 20:, Folder 17)
    - An (Box 20:, Folder 18)
    - Architects (Box 20:, Folder 19)
    - Archons (Box 20:, Folder 20)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 20:, Folder 21)
    - Attorney General (Box 20:, Folder 22)
    - Auditor's Reports (Box 20:, Folder 23)
    - B (Box 20:, Folder 24)
    - Bailey, Clark (Box 20:, Folder 25)
    - Bain, David - Coordinator, student activities (Box 20:, Folder 26)
    - Be (Box 20:, Folder 27)
    - Benton, William (Trustee) (Box 20:, Folder 28)
    - Bi (Box 20:, Folder 29)
    - Bishop, Merlin - Finance Committee (Box 20:, Folder 30)
    - Bishop, Merlin (Trustee) (Box 20:, Folder 31)
    - Bo (Box 20:, Folder 32)
    - Board agenda, 1959-1960 (Box 20:, Folder 33)
    - Board material (Box 20:, Folder 34)
    - Brammell, P. Roy (Box 20:, Folder 35)
    - Budds, John J. (Box 20:, Folder 36)
    - Budget (Box 20:, Folder 37)
    - Budget division, State (Box 20:, Folder 38)
    - Borge, Victor (Box 20:, Folder 39)
    - Campus (Box 20:, Folder 40)
    - Capital projects (Box 20:, Folder 41)
    - Carter, W. Harrison - Dean, Arts and Sciences (Box 20:, Folder 42)
    - Ce (Box 21:, Folder 1)
    - Christian, J. O. (Box 21:, Folder 2)
    - Civil Defense (Box 21:, Folder 3)
    - Clippings and releases (Box 21:, Folder 4)
    - Co (Box 21:, Folder 5)
    - Cohen, Sumner - Men's housing (Box 21:, Folder 6)
    - College entrance exam board (Box 21:, Folder 7)
    - Commencement (Box 21:, Folder 8)
    - Committee letters (Box 21:, Folder 9)
    - Committee minutes (Box 21:, Folder 10)
    - Committee reports (Box 21:, Folder 11)
    - Computer Center (Box 21:, Folder 12)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 21:, Folder 13)
    - Connecticut Council for Pre - college Science Education, Inc. (Box 21:, Folder 14)
    - Connecticut Educational Television Corporation (Box 21:, Folder 15)
    - Connecticut Foundation for Independent Schools (Box 21:, Folder 16)
    - Connecticut Higher Education Assistance Corporation (Box 21:, Folder 17)
    - Connecticut safety center (Box 21:, Folder 18)
    - Connecticut Sate Grange (Box 21:, Folder 19)
    - Contracts (Box 21:, Folder 20)
    - Coo (Box 21:, Folder 21)
    - Council for financial aid to education (Box 21:, Folder 22)
    - Cr (Box 21:, Folder 23)
    - D (Box 21:, Folder 24)
    - De (Box 21:, Folder 25)
    - Deans and directors (Box 21:, Folder 26)
    - Dining hall (Box 21:, Folder 27)
    - Directories (Box 21:, Folder 28)
    - Do (Box 21:, Folder 29)
    - Donahue, A. J. Jr. (Trustee) (Box 21:, Folder 30)
    - Dormitories (Box 21:, Folder 31)
    - Dr (Box 21:, Folder 32)
    - E (Box 21:, Folder 33)
    - Education, School of - building, 1959-1960 (Box 21:, Folder 34)
    - Education, State Department of (Box 21:, Folder 35)
    - Eisenbach, Rabbi (Box 21:, Folder 36)
    - En (Box 21:, Folder 37)
    - Enrollments (Box 21:, Folder 38)
    - F (Box 21:, Folder 39)
    - Faculty publications (Box 21:, Folder 40)
    - Finance Committee (Box 21:, Folder 41)
    - Finance and Control, Dept. of (Box 21:, Folder 42)
    - Financial statements (Box 21:, Folder 43)
    - Fine Arts building (Box 21:, Folder 44)
    - Fingles, Franklin O. (Box 21:, Folder 45)
    - Fo (Box 21:, Folder 46)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 21:, Folder 47)
    - Fraternities and sororities (Box 21:, Folder 48)
    - Fuller, Alfred C. (Trustee) (Box 21:, Folder 49)
    - Fund for the Advancement of Education (Box 21:, Folder 50)
    - G (Box 21:, Folder 51)
    - Ge (Box 21:, Folder 52)
    - Gill, Joseph N. (Trustee) (Box 21:, Folder 53)
    - Gleason, John H (Box 21:, Folder 54)
    - Governor of Connecticut - Abraham A. Ribicoff (Box 21:, Folder 55)
    - Gr (Box 21:, Folder 56)
    - H (Box 21:, Folder 57)
    - Har (Box 21:, Folder 58)
    - Hartford Branch - W. R. Griswold, supervisor (Box 21:, Folder 59)
    - Has (Box 21:, Folder 60)
    - Health Service - Dr. Leroy, director (Box 21:, Folder 61)
    - Hewitt, Harold O. - Dean, School of Pharmacy (Box 21:, Folder 62)
    - Hi (Box 21:, Folder 63)
    - Holt, Guy B. (Trustee) (Box 21:, Folder 64)
    - Hopkins, Bert E. - Dean, School of Law (Box 21:, Folder 65)
    - Honors Day (Box 21:, Folder 66)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency (Box 21:, Folder 67)
    - Hu (Box 21:, Folder 68)
    - I (Box 22:, Folder 1)
    - Inaugurations (Box 22:, Folder 2)
    - Institute of Cellular Biology (Box 22:, Folder 3)
    - Institute - counseling and guidance training (Box 22:, Folder 4)
    - Institute of Gerontology - Don P. Kent (Box 22:, Folder 5)
    - Institute of Marine Research - John S. Rankin (Box 22:, Folder 6)
    - Institute of Public Service - Beldon Schaffer (Box 22:, Folder 7)
    - Institute for Secondary School Teachers of Physics (Box 22:, Folder 8)
    - Institute for Teachers of Science, 1959-1960 (Box 22:, Folder 9)
    - Insurance (Box 22:, Folder 10)
    - Investments (Box 22:, Folder 11)
    - Invitations (Box 22:, Folder 12)
    - J (Box 22:, Folder 13)
    - Joint Council on Educational Television (Box 22:, Folder 14)
    - Joint Projects office - Allan Ostar (Box 22:, Folder 15)
    - K (Box 22:, Folder 16)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 22:, Folder 17)
    - L (Box 22:, Folder 18)
    - Labor Management Institute (Box 22:, Folder 19)
    - Land Grant bills H. R. 10876 and H.R. 10974 (Box 22:, Folder 20)
    - Land Grant College Association (Box 22:, Folder 21)
    - Law School Building (Box 22:, Folder 22)
    - Learning Resources Institute (Box 22:, Folder 23)
    - Legislation, Federal (Box 22:, Folder 24)
    - Legislation, State (Box 22:, Folder 25)
    - Li (Box 22:, Folder 26)
    - Liaison Committee (Box 22:, Folder 27)
    - Library - James E. Skipper (Box 22:, Folder 28)
    - Life Science building (Box 22:, Folder 29)
    - Lo (Box 22:, Folder 30)
    - N (Box 22:, Folder 31)
    - Mahoney, Mary H. (Trustee) (Box 22:, Folder 32)
    - Manning, Stuart H. - Director, University Extension (Box 22:, Folder 33)
    - Mansfield, J. Kenneth (Trustee) (Box 22:, Folder 34)
    - Map (Box 22:, Folder 35)
    - Maps (Box 22:, Folder 36)
    - May, Elizabeth E. - Dean, School of Home Economics (Box 22:, Folder 37)
    - McA (Box 22:, Folder 38)
    - McH (Box 22:, Folder 39)
    - McMahon, Brien, - Lecture Series (Box 22:, Folder 40)
    - McN (Box 22:, Folder 41)
    - Me (Box 22:, Folder 42)
    - Mi (Box 22:, Folder 43)
    - Military ball (Box 22:, Folder 44)
    - Military day (Box 22:, Folder 45)
    - Military department (Box 23:, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23:, Folder 2)
    - Mo (Box 23:, Folder 3)
    - N (Box 23:, Folder 4)
    - National Advisory Council on Rural Civil Defense (Box 23:, Folder 5)
    - National Advisory Panel on ROTC Affairs (NASU) (Box 23:, Folder 6)
    - National Association of State Universities (NASU), 1959-1960 (Box 23:, Folder 7)
    - National College Athletic Association (Box 23:, Folder 8)
    - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 23:, Folder 9)
    - National Education Association (Box 23:, Folder 10)
    - National Institute for Atmospheric Research (Box 23:, Folder 11)
    - National Library Week (Box 23:, Folder 12)
    - National Planning Association (Box 23:, Folder 13)
    - National Research Foundation (Box 23:, Folder 14)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 23:, Folder 15)
    - Nelson, Don (Box 23:, Folder 16)
    - New England Board of Higher Education (Box 23:, Folder 17)
    - New England Council (Box 23:, Folder 18)
    - New England Land Grant Universities (Box 23:, Folder 19)
    - North dormitories (Box 23:, Folder 20)
    - Northby, Arwood S. (Box 23:, Folder 21)
    - Nuclear reactor (Box 23:, Folder 22)
    - O (Box 23:, Folder 23)
    - P (Box 23:, Folder 24)
    - Peterson, M. Elizabeth (Trustee) (Box 23:, Folder 25)
    - Pharmacy Research addition (Box 23:, Folder 26)
    - Physical Science building (Box 23:, Folder 27)
    - Pictures (Box 23:, Folder 28)
    - Pl (Box 23:, Folder 29)
    - Policies, University (various) (Box 23:, Folder 30)
    - Powers, John E. - Director, Placement (Box 23:, Folder 31)
    - President's Committee on Education Beyond High School (Box 23:, Folder 32)
    - President's Committee on Scientists and Engineers (Box 23:, Folder 33)
    - Public Works Department (Box 23:, Folder 34)
    - Q (Box 23:, Folder 35)
    - R (Box 24:, Folder 1)
    - Re (Box 24:, Folder 2)
    - Real Estate (Box 24:, Folder 3)
    - Regional Vocational Agriculture Center (Box 24:, Folder 4)
    - Religious education (Box 24:, Folder 5)
    - Research corporation (Box 24:, Folder 6)
    - Research foundation (Box 24:, Folder 7)
    - Research grants (Box 24:, Folder 8)
    - Ro (Box 24:, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 24:, Folder 10)
    - Ryan, J. Ray (Box 24:, Folder 11)
    - S (Box 24:, Folder 12)
    - Sanders, William J. (Box 24:, Folder 13)
    - Sch (Box 24:, Folder 14)
    - Schneller, Richard F., 1959-1960 (Box 24:, Folder 15)
    - Scholarship committee (Box 24:, Folder 16)
    - Scholarships, financial aids and gifts (Box 24:, Folder 17)
    - Scholarships, etc. (Box 24:, Folder 18)
    - Science talent awards (Box 24:, Folder 19)
    - Se (Box 24:, Folder 20)
    - Sh (Box 24:, Folder 21)
    - Shippee, Lester E. (Box 24:, Folder 22)
    - Si (Box 24:, Folder 23)
    - Sistare, Willard M. - Manager, Auditorium (Box 24:, Folder 24)
    - Sm (Box 24:, Folder 25)
    - South dormitory (Box 24:, Folder 26)
    - Speaking engagements and meetings (Box 24:, Folder 27)
    - Speaking engagements and meetings - regrets (Box 24:, Folder 28)
    - Speeches (Box 24:, Folder 29)
    - Spielman, Arliss A. (Box 24:, Folder 30)
    - St (Box 24:, Folder 31)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 24:, Folder 32)
    - State Building Commission (Box 24:, Folder 33)
    - State Development Commission (Box 24:, Folder 34)
    - State Highway Department (Box 24:, Folder 35)
    - State personnel (Box 24:, Folder 36)
    - State Public Utilities (Box 24:, Folder 37)
    - State Universities Association (Box 24:, Folder 38)
    - Sti (Box 24:, Folder 39)
    - Student Senate (Box 24:, Folder 40)
    - Student - letter re (Box 24:, Folder 41)
    - Student Union Board and building (Box 24:, Folder 42)